https://www.uis.cam.ac.uk/privacy-and-cookie-policies

Introduction
This page explains what personal information we gather when you visit this web site.
Who will process my personal information?
The information published here applies to the use of your personal information (also known as 'personal data') by the University of Cambridge through the viewing or use of this site.
General personal information collected on our websites
When you visit any of the websites within the Cambridge domain we hold certain information about you for service and security reasons. For more information on this, please see
https://www.cam.ac.uk/about-this-site/privacy-policy
Further information
For more information about how we handle your personal information, and your rights under data protection legislation, please see
https://www.information-compliance.admin.cam.ac.uk/data-protection/general-data
Cookies
Users who visit a Falcon site may receive some or all of the Google Analytics cookies if the site administrator has enabled them (whether or not they authenticate).
Sites may embed third-party material (e.g. YouTube videos) and these may carry their own cookies. You must refer to the site's local cookie policy to determine what cookies are being set and for what purpose.
Sites may include 'ShareThis' social media buttons, which will carry cookies if the user has a 'ShareThis' account enabled.
Users who authenticate will receive cookies from the Raven/Shibboleth authentication system.
CookieReturned toFunctionP/S*__utma
Falcon site
Google Analytics
P
__utmb
Falcon site
Google Analytics
P
P
_shibsession_...
shib.raven.cam.ac.uk
Authentication
S
Ucam-WLS-Session
shib.raven.cam.ac.uk
Authentication
S
JSESSIONID
__stid
Set by "ShareThis" widget if it is embedded on the site. The ShareThis service can identify a visitor if they have separately signed up with ShareThis for a ShareThis account (and provided their consent). This information may be used to display advertisements on sites that include the ShareThis sharing icon - See 'ShareThis' privacy statement.
Social Media buttons
P
*Final column: S marks a session cookie. P marks a persistent cookie.
Session cookies expire when the user quits the browser (or earlier).
Persistent cookies remain within the browser after it is quit and restarted, until they reach their expiry date.
Raven privacy & cookie policy:
http://raven.cam.ac.uk/privacy.html
Google analytics cookie policy:
http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html
UIS Service Desk
Self-service portal  servicedesk@uis.cam.ac.uk  01223 332999
UIS Service Status
Service status line: (01223 7)67999  Sign up for SMS/email status alerts  Read major IT incident reports
UIS bITe-size bulletin
A regular newsletter aimed at the University's IT community, highlighting service and project news from UIS.
Postal Address:
Roger Needham Building
7 JJ Thomson Avenue
Cambridge CB3 0RB
01223 337733
Information provided by:
UIS staff wiki (UIS login required)
UIS staff intranet (UIS login required)
Spotlight on...
About research at Cambridge
